我们之前说到使用在Sunshine应用中使用Intent来启动Activity并且
We've talked about using intents within Sunshine to start activities and send
在应用间发送数据  但如果你要群发信息给
data between apps. But what if you want to broadcast a message to
多个应用呢  举个例子  系统要广播一个消息  说
many apps? For example, the system will broadcast a message, saying that the
设备正在充电或者刚刚重启完  我们的方法是
device is charging or that it's just finished rebooting. To do that ourselves,
使用sendBroadcast()方法来广播一个Intent  然后这些广播
we use the SendBroadcast method to broadcast an intent. And those broadcasts
就会被广播接收器接收到  通常
are received by broadcast receivers, typically
简称为接收器  使用Intent
referred to as simply, receivers. Using intent
过滤器  就像我们之前看到的一样  它们会表明哪些广播是自己
filters, like the ones we saw earlier, they indicate which broadcast they're
感兴趣的  所以如果我们返回到之前信封的比喻
interested in. So if we return to our envelope metaphor from earlier, in
在广播Intent的情况下  你的
the case of a broadcast intent, your
你的信封会被发送给任一
envelope is basically addressed to any broadcast receiver
对此事件感兴趣的广播接收器
that's interested in knowing that this event has
而它正是通过Intent过滤器来实现的
happened. And it does that using intent filter.
所以Intent  也就是广播  会被传送给
So intents, which are broadcast, are transmitted to every
带有特定广播接收器的应用  它们的广播接收器的
app with a broadcast receiver that has an intent
Intent过滤器会告诉系统哪些消息是它感兴趣
filter telling the system your ideas are intriguing to
因而会为终端用户订阅这些消息
me and I wish to subscribe to end user.